Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Rolled Drawings, 582 Linear feet in 142 boxes.
  - New York
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Foundation & piling plans (Offsite-box RD-012, Tube 037)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Granite work & Terra cotta work (Offsite-box RD-003, Tube 007-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Granite work & Terra cotta work (Offsite-box RD-003, Tube 007-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Large working drawings on linen (Offsite-box RD-107, Tube 341-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Large working drawings on linen (Offsite-box RD-107, Tube 341-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Linen drawings (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 280-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Linen drawings (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 280-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Original drawings & boiler house (Offsite-box RD-008, Tube 027)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Proposed new building & alterations (Offsite-box RD-055, Tube 188-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Proposed new building & alterations (Offsite-box RD-056, Tube 188-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Seven drawings (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 229)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange (Offsite-box RD-127, Tube 400)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange (Offsite-box RD-127, Tube 401)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange (Offsite-box RD-127, Tube 402)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange (Offsite-box RD-128, Tube 403)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange (Offsite-box RD-128, Tube 404)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Alterations to Luncheon Club (Offsite-box RD-025, Tube 077)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Drawings on linen, steel work? (Offsite-box RD-094, Tube 306)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Green prints -- plumbing (Offsite-box RD-095, Tube 309)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Ink on linen -- complete architectural (Offsite-box RD-095, Tube 307)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Ink on linen -- structural drawings (Offsite-box RD-105, Tube 333-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Ink on linen -- structural drawings (Offsite-box RD-105, Tube 333-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Ink on paper, presentation drawings (Offsite-box RD-078, Tube 263)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Interior finish (Offsite-box RD-024, Tube 073)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Large scale architectural & blueprints (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 348)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Stock Exchange | Large scale architectural & blueprints (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 349)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Opdycke, L. E. | 119 & 121 East 69th Street | All scale drawings (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 045)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Office Building (Park Place & Greenwich Street) (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 149)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Park Place | All drawings (Offsite-box RD-021, Tube 064)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Park Place | All drawings (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 068)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Park Place | All drawings (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 070)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Park Place | All drawings (Offsite-box RD-024, Tube 072)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Peters, T. M. | Residence (13 East 94th Street) (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 080)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Post, A. U. Z. | Residence (Bedford Street) | alterations (Offsite-box RD-052, Tube 176)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Post & Flagg | Office Building (49-51 Broad Street) (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 239)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Post & Flagg | Office Building (Offsite-box RD-078, Tube 262)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Robbins, G. A. | Residence (East 36th Street) (Offsite-box RD-018, Tube 053-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Robbins, G. A. | Residence (East 36th Street) (Offsite-box RD-018, Tube 053-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (101 Park Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-003, Tube 009)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (Offsite-box RD-060, Tube 201-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (Offsite-box RD-060, Tube 201-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (Offsite-box RD-060, Tube 201-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 235)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 240)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 111)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Cloth prints (Offsite-box RD-115, Tube 366)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Cloth prints (Offsite-box RD-115, Tube 367)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Key plans (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 224)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Record set of contract drawings (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 061-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Roosevelt Hotel | Turkish Bath (Offsite-box RD-041, Tube 137)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Rutgerstown | A & B Units (Offsite-box RD-018, Tube 054)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-057, Tube 194-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-057, Tube 194-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-089, Tube 295-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-089, Tube 295-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-090, Tube 297-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-090, Tube 297-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box RD-090, Tube 297-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Schermerhorn | Stores (Broadway & 4th Street) (Offsite-box RD-015, Tube 047)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Schneider | Proposed Apartment (107th Street) (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 105)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Schroeder, J. Langdon | Webster Apartments -- set of blueprints (Offsite-box RD-029, Tube 089-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Shattuck Building (Reade Street & Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-024, Tube 074)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Shattuck Building (Reade Street & Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 081)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Shattuck Building (Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 082)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Shattuck Building (Reade Street & Broadway) | Surveys (Offsite-box RD-029, Tube 089-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Shattuck Building (Offsite-box RD-045, Tube 154)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Sheltering Arms (122-124 East 29th Street) (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 086)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Stores (636-638 Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-060, Tube 202)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Tiffany, Mrs. | Additions to house (65 East 66th Street) (Offsite-box RD-025, Tube 079)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Times Building (Offsite-box RD-098, Tube 317-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Times Building (Offsite-box RD-099, Tube 317-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Train, A. C. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-022, Tube 066)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Train, A. C. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 227-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Vincent Building (Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-099, Tube 318-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Vincent Building (Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-099, Tube 318-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Vincent Building (Broadway) (Offsite-box RD-103, Tube 329)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Warwick Hotel (Offsite-box RD-085, Tube 288-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Warwick Hotel (Offsite-box RD-085, Tube 288-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Warwick Hotel (N.E. corner 6th Avenue & 54th Street) | Cloth tracings, plans, elevations, electric, etc. (Offsite-box RD-113, Tube 358)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Warwick Hotel (N.E. corner 6th Avenue & 54th Street) | Cloth tracings, plans, elevations, electric, etc. (Offsite-box RD-112, Tube 358-Annex)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | White Estate | Hotel (Offsite-box RD-030, Tube 094)
    - New York—NYC—Queens | 1939 New York World's Fair | Netherlands Building (Offsite-box RD-109, Tube 347-A)
    - New York—NYC—Queens | 1939 New York World's Fair | Netherlands Building (Offsite-box RD-109, Tube 347-B)
    - New York—NYC—Queens | 1939 New York World's Fair | Netherlands Building (Offsite-box RD-109, Tube 347-C)
    - New York—NYC—Queens (Belle Harbor) | Allen, George | Houses (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 110)
    - New York—Oswego | Higgins, John D. | Residence alterations & additions (Offsite-box RD-045, Tube 152)
    - New York—Oswego | Pontiac Hotel (Offsite-box RD-101, Tube 323)
    - New York—Oyster Bay | Kirkwood Cottage (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 219)
    - New York—Oyster Bay | Peters Estate | Development plans (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 082)
    - New York—Oyster Bay | Peters Estate | Proposed development (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 150)
    - New York—Poughkeepsie | Vassar Brothers Hospital (Offsite-box RD-064, Tube 217)
    - New York—Schenectady | Union College | Science Building (Offsite-box RD-062, Tube 207)
    - New York—Schenectady | Union College | Gymnasium (Offsite-box RD-074, Tube 245)
    - New York—Schenectady | Van Curler Hotel | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-104, Tube 331-A)
    - New York—Schenectady | Van Curler Hotel | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-104, Tube 331-B)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | Gould's Hotel (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 069)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | Gould Manufacturing Co. (Office Building) (Offsite-box RD-054, Tube 183)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | Gould Manufacturing Co. | Additions (Offsite-box RD-056, Tube 189)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | Gould Manufacturing Co. (16 Murray Street) | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 237)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | Gould Office Building (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 222-B)
    - New York—Seneca Falls | Gould, G. H. | House [Hotel?] (Offsite-box RD-063, Tube 213)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel | Original steel plans & original sketches (Offsite-box RD-100, Tube 320-A)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel | Original steel plans & original sketches (Offsite-box RD-100, Tube 320-B)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel | Electric Plans, heating & ventilation, framing (Offsite-box RD-102, Tube 326)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel [rolls 1 & 2 of 6] (Offsite-box RD-138, Tube ###-###)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel [roll 3 of 6] (Offsite-box RD-139, Tube ###)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel [roll 4 of 6] (Offsite-box RD-140, Tube ###)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel [roll 5 of 6] (Offsite-box RD-141, Tube ###)
    - New York—Syracuse | Syracuse Hotel [roll 6 of 6] (Offsite-box RD-142, Tube ###)
    - New York—Troy | Samaritan Hospital | All scales (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 012-014)
    - New York—Troy | Samaritan Hospital | Maternity Ward (Offsite-box RD-009, Tube 030-A)
    - New York—Troy | Samaritan Hospital | Maternity Ward (Offsite-box RD-010, Tube 030-B)
    - New York—Troy | Samaritan Hospital (Offsite-box RD-084, Tube 282-A)
    - New York—Troy | Samaritan Hospital (Offsite-box RD-084, Tube 282-B)
    - New York—Troy | Troy Savings Bank | Plan of original buildings (Offsite-box RD-016, Tube 049-A)
    - New York—Troy | Troy Savings Bank | Plan of original buildings | Annex (Offsite-box RD-016, Tube 049-B)
    - New York—Troy | Troy Savings Bank | Plan of original buildings (Offsite-box RD-016, Tube 049-C)
    - New York—Tuxedo Park | Corey, Fred | House (formerly Lewsi [Lewis?] residence) (Offsite-box RD-037, Tube 121)
    - New York—West Point | Thayer Hotel (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 298-A)
    - New York—West Point | Thayer Hotel (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 298-B)
    - New York—West Point | Thayer Hotel (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 298-C)
    - New York—Yonkers | Yonkers Apartments | Proposed apartments (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 219)
  - Ohio
    - Ohio—Akron | Sieberling Residence (Offsite-box RD-088, Tube 294-A)
    - Ohio—Akron | Sieberling Residence (Offsite-box RD-088, Tube 294-B)
    - Ohio—Akron | Sieberling Residence (Offsite-box RD-088, Tube 294-C)
    - Ohio—Cincinnati | Granden Court Apartments (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 221)
    - Ohio—Cincinnati | Sinton Hotel (Offsite-box RD-132, Tube 283)
    - Ohio—Cincinnati | Sinton Hotel (Offsite-box RD-087, Tube 293-A)
    - Ohio—Cincinnati | Sinton Hotel (Offsite-box RD-088, Tube 293-B)
    - Ohio—Cincinnati | Sinton Hotel | Addition (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 244)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Baine Building (Offsite-box RD-030, Tube 093)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Baine Building (Offsite-box RD-081, Tube 276)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Brothers, W. V. | Ansonia Apartments (Ansel Road & Edmunds Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 230)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Chamber of Commerce (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 148)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 061-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-029, Tube 092)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Child's Building (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 110)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Hotel (Offsite-box RD-097, Tube 314)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Jewish Hospital (Offsite-box RD-001, Tube 001-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Jewish Hospital (Offsite-box RD-001, Tube 001-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-031, Tube 100-101)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-051, Tube 172)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-056, Tube 190)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-082, Tube 277-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-082, Tube 277-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-085, Tube 286)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-085, Tube 287)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-095, Tube 310)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-095, Tube 311-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-096, Tube 311-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-096, Tube 311-C)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-105, Tube 334)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-106, Tube 336-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company (55th Street & Woodland Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-106, Tube 336-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Iron Works (Offsite-box RD-130, Tube 308)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Lorain Bank (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 239)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Perry Branch (Offsite-box RD-062, Tube 210-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Perry Branch (Offsite-box RD-063, Tube 210-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Perry Branch | All drawings (Offsite-box RD-063, Tube 211)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Wade Park Bank Branch (Offsite-box RD-131, Tube 271)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Wade Park Bank Branch (Offsite-box RD-087, Tube 292-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Wade Park Bank Branch (Offsite-box RD-087, Tube 292-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Cleveland Trust Company | Wade Park Bridge [Branch?] Addition (Offsite-box RD-080, Tube 269)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 130)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building (Offsite-box RD-047, Tube 163-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building (Offsite-box RD-048, Tube 163-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building (Offsite-box RD-048, Tube 163-C)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Building (Offsite-box RD-061, Tube 206)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Euclid Gardens (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 147)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Fenway Hall (Offsite-box RD-050, Tube 170)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Ginn, Frank H. | Residence | Scale drawings (Offsite-box RD-041, Tube 139)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Ginn, Frank H. | Residence | Miscellaneous drawings (Offsite-box RD-056, Tube 191)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Hollenden Hotel | Alterations & additions (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 144)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Hollenden Hotel (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 146)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | McNutt-McCall | Housing Development (St. Clair Park) (Offsite-box RD-042, Tube 140)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Mount Sinai Hospital (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 243)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 151)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (East 24th Street & Euclid Avenue) | Elev., plans, sections, etc. / electrical, plumbing (Offsite-box RD-113, Tube 362-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (East 24th Street & Euclid Avenue) | Elev., plans, sections, etc. / electrical, plumbing (Offsite-box RD-114, Tube 362-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (East 24th Street & Euclid Avenue) | Elev., plans, sections, etc. / electrical, plumbing (Offsite-box RD-114, Tube 363)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (East 24th Street & Euclid Avenue) | Elev., plans, sections, etc. / electrical, plumbing (Offsite-box RD-114, Tube 364)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (East 24th Street & Euclid Avenue) | Elev., plans, sections, etc. / electrical, plumbing (Offsite-box RD-114, Tube 365)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | National Town & Country Club (Thompson Street) (Offsite-box RD-061, Tube 204)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Newcomer Apartments (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 236)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Newcomer Apartments | Key plans (Offsite-box RD-077, Tube 259)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Office Building (Euclid Avenue & 102nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-017, Tube 051)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Office Building (Euclid Avenue & 102nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-053, Tube 180)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Office Building (Euclid Avenue & 102nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-053, Tube 181)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Office Building (Euclid Avenue & 102nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-054, Tube 182-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Office Building (Euclid Avenue & 102nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-054, Tube 182-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Proposed commercial buildings (Euclid Avenue & 18th Street) (Offsite-box RD-015, Tube 047)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Proposed Hotel, club, & stores (Euclid Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 081)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Proposed Hotel & Office Building (Euclid Avenue & East 9th Street) (Offsite-box RD-063, Tube 212)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Store & bachelor apartment building (Euclid Avenue & 105th Street) (Offsite-box RD-018, Tube 054)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Wade Park Manor (Offsite-box RD-010, Tube 031-032)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Wade Park Manor (Offsite-box RD-104, Tube 332-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Wade Park Manor (Offsite-box RD-104, Tube 332-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-002, Tube 005)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-098, Tube 316)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-100, Tube 321-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-101, Tube 321-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-101, Tube 324-A)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building (Offsite-box RD-102, Tube 324-B)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Williamson Building | Proposed alterations, 1907-1914 (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 146)
    - Ohio—Cleveland | Windmere Savings Bank & Loan (Offsite-box RD-058, Tube 195)
    - Ohio—Hamilton | Anthony Wayne Hotel (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 116-A)
    - Ohio—Hamilton | Anthony Wayne Hotel (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 116-B)
  - Pennsylvania
    - Pennsylvania—Kingston | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-022, Tube 065)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Carnegie Tech (Offsite-box RD-143, Tube 345)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Park Building (5th Avenue & Smithfield Street) (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 233-A)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Park Building (5th Avenue & Smithfield Street) (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 233-B)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Park Building (5th Avenue & Smithfield Street) (Offsite-box RD-107, Tube 339)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Pennsylvania Hotel (Offsite-box RD-019, Tube 056)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Pennsylvania Hotel | Proposed plans (Offsite-box RD-038, Tube 126)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Pittsburgh Bank (Offsite-box RD-094, Tube 305-A)
    - Pennsylvania—Pittsburgh | Pittsburgh Bank (Offsite-box RD-094, Tube 305-B)
    - Pennsylvania—Rochester | Penn Beaver Hotel (Offsite-box RD-110, Tube 350-B)
  - Rhode Island
    - Rhode Island—Jamestown | Proposed hotel (Offsite-box RD-017, Tube 051)
  - Virginia
    - Virginia—Charlotte | Thomas Jefferson Inn (Offsite-box RD-101, Tube 322)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Cradock (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 231-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Cradock (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 231-B)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Proposed plans (Offsite-box RD-001, Tube 002-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Proposed plans (Offsite-box RD-001, Tube 002-B)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development (Offsite-box RD-002, Tube 002-C)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | apartments & stores (Offsite-box RD-007, Tube 023)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Framing plans (Offsite-box RD-008, Tube 028-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Framing plans (Offsite-box RD-009, Tube 028-B)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Lithographs (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 085)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Schedules of houses (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 086)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Apartment buildings (Offsite-box RD-028, Tube 089-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Details of doors (Offsite-box RD-029, Tube 091)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Glenwood Tract (Offsite-box RD-031, Tube 100-101)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Glenwood Tract (Offsite-box RD-038, Tube 124)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Blueprint set (Offsite-box RD-040, Tube 132)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Framing plans (Offsite-box RD-041, Tube 138)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Motion picture building (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 224)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Motion picture building (Offsite-box RD-074, Tube 247)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development (Offsite-box RD-130, Tube 268)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Plant in plans (Offsite-box RD-089, Tube 296-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Plant in plans (Offsite-box RD-089, Tube 296-B)